Hello everyone, I'm Kobashi and I'm here today at Wanty Lin Dome Nagoya.
I'm here today to perform an emergency ceremony for the Samurai Japan vs Chunichi match.
Something amazing happened... and you could see it...
Japan is...
I'm wearing it. I'm sorry.
Samurai Japan, I'm sorry.
Yes, I'm wearing the uniform... but the ceremony is less than an hour away.
I've been doing a lot of interviews and other things.
I've been doing a lot of interviews and other things that I'm very thankful for, and it's only now that I have time to film the opening ceremony.
I'd like to know what I was doing before the first pitch, and what I was doing before I shot this video.
Please take a look.
That's him.
The proof is in the pudding. I talked to the NPP and the judicial branch.
By "hit," I mean...
It was really an arbitrary deviation.
Yes, sir.
Please.
I'll take it.
Thank you very much.
Bon appétit!
Nice ball.
Nice ball!
Ha-ha-ha!
Ah!
Good morning
Good morning, sir.
What's your name?
I'm Hiroto Takahashi.
Pleased to meet you.
I'm here to take you back to Nagoya.
I'm Mr. Iwai.
Pleased to meet you.
I have a tan from Horlicks.
I'm sorry, I'm very busy.
How can I help you?
I'm sure you'll get it to him.
I'd like to.
I think I can do it here.
Let's give it a try.
Please do.
I'm sorry.
Stretch it out.
Are you okay?
Thank you very much.
Looks like it's moving. He's throwing out the first pitch somewhere.
Two and a half.
One inning delivered, sir.
Are you okay?
Nervous.
Rakuten fan.
Are you a Rakuten fan?
Enemy, enemy, enemy!
Shall we go home?
I don't think so.
I think Mr. Satozaki taught you that, too.
Want me to count them?
One.
One, two, three.
Can we go now?
Go straight ahead.
Thank you.
When you get to the show, please go higher.
Higher. Yes, sir. Thank you very much.
Knight.
Yes!
Thank you for your hard work.
It's a nerve-wracking environment besides number 3.
No, not at all. With number 3, too.
There's about 40,000 people there.
But if you're singing for 40,000 people, you'll be fine.
No, it's fine.
Only a few of us need 40,000 people.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Is it too many?
Yes, it's a lot.
How many will we get?
At most, 60,000 so far.
You're a funny guy.
No, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
That's it.
Let's go.
Put it on.
Thank you very much!
Thank you!
Remember, two more hours.
I'll remember!
Nice goal!
Thank you!
I'm 19.
I'm 20.
We are classmates.
My height is changing.
I'll give you a guess.
Yes, cheese!
Thank you!Thank you!
This is Shiori Kubo from Nogizaka46!
Ms. Kubo, Ms. Kubo, where are you?
Yes, hello everyone!
I am Yori Kinoshita from Nakamoto Technical Office.
I am currently on the ground.
I am in front of the Samurai Japan editorial board.
I would like to say that Yoshinobu Yamamoto, the head of the company, has come to see us.
I would like to talk with you.
Please give my best regards.
First of all, I would like to receive the WGC's
Please listen to what he has to say.
Anyway, you are the best in the world, and I will do my best to make it there.
I would like to play. Thank you very much for your support.
Thank you very much.
That's all for now, from the stadium, Allosaurus Court.
I was nervous.
It looks like the money is going to bat now.
May I?
Excuse me, one more time.
Yes, one more time.
There you go.
Thank you very much.
Oh, seriously?
Ending
So, the first pitch is coming up soon, but first, a quick look back.
Pitching practice. Was that really practice? So, Takahashi, Miyai, Sato, and Miyagi came to teach us how to pitch on short notice.
I was really surprised. It was really a surprise and I was very nervous.
They were very kind and told me that they would definitely be able to reach me.
There was no way I could not let him reach me.
Mr. Satozaki has been teaching me how to pitch, right? He was teaching me how to pitch during this Uesaka distribution.
And Mr. Satozaki taught me.
One, two, three, you decided to pitch.
Yes, I can never fail. And Mr. Satozaki is here today. He will be giving a commentary.
Mr. Satosaki, I will do my best.
At that time, we were talking about how we were waiting for the four-ball ceremony.
I didn't think it would be decided at Samurai Japan.
I was so nervous that I had to give an interview.
Yes, I was. The interview was also nerve-wracking.
It was decided on short notice that my sister, Mr. Ishimoto, would come.
She was here the whole time, waiting for me.
And then, in the back, there was the Samurai Japan bench right in front of me, and Ryuichi Sasaki, the pitcher, was also there.
I think Ryuichi Sasaki was there, too, but I was too nervous to see him.
But I was too nervous to see them. I was too nervous to see them. I was really sorry.
I saw Ohtani's putting practice, hitting practice, and so on.
I even got to see that much. It was amazing.
The moment Otani entered the box
I could see all the players coming up to him as soon as he entered the box.
I could hear the players saying, "Oh, man, he's in trouble.
To be able to see him from that distance was really
I thought, "I really don't want this to happen in my life.
In the meantime, it looks like you are going to be called up soon.
I can never get used to it. No matter how many times I do the examinations, I never get used to it.
Every time I'm freshly nervous, and every time I'm nervous, I'm nervous in a different way.
I really appreciate the warm reception I received during the stadium report earlier.
Ah! Let's go, let's go!
Yes! I'm off!
Thank you for watching!
Let's go!
This is Ushiori Kubo of Nogizaka 46!
Please give an urgent ceremony with encouragement!
Nice pinch!
Next notice
It's time to enjoy the game!
Apple juice!
Apple juice from the inn.
Yum!
I didn't expect it to arrive.
And now, right in front of me...
Sasaki Laiki is on the mound.
I can't believe we were throwing from the same spot
at the same age.
It's the first time I'm seeing Laiki pitching in person.
I think this day is a dream.
Always. I'm so glad I picked him.
Oh, yes, yes.
I'd be happy if I clap my hands
I'd be happy if my clapping hands would be played in the stadium.
I was wondering if it would be better to use one of
I thought it would be better to use one of our best-known songs, but...
But you said I could use my favorite song.
I was so happy.
I was so happy!
I don't know...
I didn't want it to be in the mountain yet.
The cheering song is now in session, too!
So the air in the stadium is hot again
That's great.
I just came up with something like a peon.
I want to go to all the stadiums.
want to go to all the stadiums.
I heard that we're going to put out for the whole year.
I see.
Well, I'll tell you what I'll do in private.
I'll take some trivial video.
I went to what stadium today, too.
I'll just take a video of me going to the stadium.
I wonder if I'll be able to visit all the stadiums in a year.
Kondo, you're really something.Wow, Kondo really is a player!
He scored a goal!
Fujiwara is amazing.
Three bases are loaded, and with two outs...
The spiral continued.
Shunji Yanagi!
Toshiyuki Ono and Toshiyuki Yanagi.
I can't believe I got to see that in one day.
Amazing.
It's the same age relay.
The only one.
That's what I just learned.
And they're both the same age.
The only two people in Samurai Japan who are the same age.
They were teaching us right up until the last minute.
Higashi Noboru Miyagi...
He's standing on the mound.
It's a rare moment.
Just now, Viciedo
Viciedo was really sticking it out against Laiki.
I'm amazed he could hit 165 kilos that hard.
Against 165 kilograms.
It's amazing.
Thank you for watching our games.
Amazing!
Tanaka?
Mikiya Tanaka.
As I recall, um...
Show Music Dragons
A fan of the show music dragons
Might have told me about him.
I think I may have heard of him.
Maybe you've heard of him.
Tanaka Mikiya.
I've been paying attention to him.
I think you told me about him.
That's great.
I've seen a lot of fans, a lot of different teams.
Fans of different teams come to our booth, so they tell us about them.
They tell me about it.
This year's
They tell me who their favorite player is on their favorite team.
and so on.
I really appreciate it, as a person who wants to know about various teams
As someone who wants to know about various teams, I really appreciate it!
Ah! Kai Cannon!
Wow, I knew Kai was a great player.
That's amazing.
I stabbed him.
Kai cannon!
He stabbed it!
For the driving ceremony.
I'm afraid I have to change.
But I've seen too much of the game.
I chose to watch it.
This inning
It's the top of the 6th inning
After the end of the table
I'd like to change my clothes at Mach
Apparently.
Oh, wow! That's great!
Straight off the pace!
Two bases!
Kondo is amazing!
That's the second time today!
Two bases!
That's amazing!
It was a low pitch, but it flew!
That's fun.
There's still no outs, so here's your chance.
Good thing I didn't go change my clothes.
Hey, what if something happens to me here on the sixth floor?
Hey, general.
Hey...
Chance for Nakanami...
Support Samurai.
Nakano, from Yamagata
This is an interesting defensive position when he's ready to bunt.
He's out in front of the batter.
He's good!
That's good.
His defensive position is pretty low.
Grain height.
Utaro Sunclear
dezxy
I was just about to go change my clothes.
I was just about to go change when Hiroto Takahashi came out.
I quit.
He might get mad at me.
I told him to hurry up and get ready.
I want to see it.
He said 157.
Oh, my God.
I can't get dressed.
We'll get you dressed here.
I can get dressed smoothly.
I'm dressed.
Nice kitchen!
Mr. Takahashi!
Nice goal!
Mr. Takada, you're dressed?Mr. Takada, you're changing?
Did you do that seven times?
I can't take this anymore.
I haven't put on socks yet.
You haven't even put on your jacket.
Have you ever seen a uniform like this? I'm sorry, I don't like it.
I'm sorry, I don't mean to be rude, I really don't.
This is too shocking.
There's something like that, isn't there?
I've been watching the game now.
I have to go get ready for the driving ceremony.
I'd like to go.
I just finished getting dressed.
It's a lot of money, isn't it?
I'll be cheering for you while I continue to get ready for the ceremony.
I'm off!
We're going to have a driving ceremony now.
I'll be handing out the cheering flags to the riders on behalf of all of you!
Thank you, Director Furuyama!
Next, on behalf of the fans of Samurai Japan.
I would like to thank Ms. Shiori Kubo, 46 Nogizaka, who has performed today's ceremony.
Ms. Shiori Kubo from Nogizaka46 will present a letter of support for Samurai Japan!
It was written in hopes that Samurai Japan will be the best in the world!
It's a heartfelt message for Samurai Japan to be the best in the world!
Now, Ms. Kubo, please.
And with that, the day of Dzong has come to an end!
Thank you very much!
We really had a dream-like day!
It was a day that I thought was a dream!
I was surrounded by really kind people who taught me how to pitch.
I was able to win the game, too!
Samurai Japan had a really wonderful day!
I remember the feeling of the stadium coming together as one.
I was able to share that passionate moment with them.
To be able to share that passion together
I felt that it is really only possible in baseball.
I promised myself that I would continue to love baseball from now on.
Mr. Satozaki also taught me how to pitch.
There are still many members who love baseball.
I hope that everyone will be able to participate in various activities in the future.
I hope to be a member of Nogizaka Baseball Club more and more so that we can be involved in various activities.
I would like to work harder and harder as a member of the Nogizaka Baseball Club.
I would like to work even harder as a member of the Nogizaka Baseball Club so that we can be involved in various activities.
I would like to make more and more videos with everyone this year.
Personally, this year, I set a goal to conquer all stadiums.
I'm thinking of going around the country to various places with the goal of conquering all stadiums.
It was a day that really made me love baseball even more!
And now the main game is about to start!
All I can do is to cheer for the team, even though it's really only a small effort.
I hope that my message will be conveyed to the audience.
I'll be cheering for you all the way!
Please do your best to regain the number one position in the world!
That's all for now, it was a day of fist weaving!
Thank you very much!
My heart is full
If you thought this video was good, if you want to watch baseball, if you want to love baseball, if you want to watch baseball
If you want to watch baseball, if you love baseball, if you want to watch baseball, if you love baseball, if you want to watch baseball, if you want to watch baseball
Please subscribe to our channel and click the "Good" button!
Bye, bye, bye!